Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 5: Boxes 89-110
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 5: Boxes 89-110
- Box: 110, Folder: 10 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Teamwork: Vol. 7, No. 11, Publication (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Teamwork: Vol. 7, No. 10, Publication (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Teamwork: Vol. 7, No. 3, Publication (Box 110, Folder 10)
    March 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Report on Apprentice Training Program of the Tennessee Valley Authority, Publication (Box 110, Folder 10)
    July 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Labor-Management Relations in TVA, Publication (Box 110, Folder 10)
    May 12, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Employee Training in TVA During Wartime Expansion, Publication (Box 110, Folder 10)
    By William J. McGlothlin. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: TVA's Training Program for Chemical Plant Operations, Publication (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: Are You Safe at Home? Fire Prevention: Bulletin 8, Publication (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Item 20: "Once for All" Story of the Consolidated Welfare Fund, Publication (Box 110, Folder 10)
- Box: 110, Folder: 11 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: A Bibliography for the TVA Program, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
    January 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: TVA Today, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
    1965-1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: TVA and Private Enterprise, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Fertilizer Science and the American Farmer: The Research and Education Programs of the Tennessee Valley Authority, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: TVA Power, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
    1957-1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Facts About TVA Operations, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: TVA and its Critics, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: General Agreement between the Tennessee Valley Authoriu and the Tennessee Valley Trades and Labor Council covering Annual Employment, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
    Revised July1, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Employee Relationship Policy, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: Employee Relationship Policy, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: A Step Forward in Labor-Management Relations, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Item 12: A Bibliography for the TVA Program, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
    January 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: TVA Flood Control, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Item 14: Some Questions for the Critics of TVA, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
    By Gordon R. Clapp. September 30, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Guidelines: Union-Management Cooperative Program, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Item 16: Teamwork Approach to Productivity, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
    By Thelma Iles Dodd. January, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Cooperative Program of the Tennessee Valley Trades and Labor Council and the Tennessee Valley Authority, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Item 18: Guidelines: Union-Management Cooperative Program, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Item 19: Industrial Democracy on the TVA: A Pilot Report, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
    By Orvia Collins. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Articles of Agreement between the Tennessee Valley Authority and the Salary Policy Employee Panel, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
    Negotiated December 5, 1950, Revised May 1, 1952 and February 4, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Suggestions Handled by TVA Trades and Labor Cooperative Committees, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
    May 1954-April 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Plan for Union-Management Cooperative Conference Program Between TVA and the Salary Policy Employee Panel, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Item 23: Union Management Cooperation in Action, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
    March 8-9, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Plan for Joint Cooperative Conference Program between TVA and the Salary Policy Employee Panel, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Item 25: Employee Relations in TVA, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Item 26: General Joint Cooperative Committee: The Cooperative Committee Program of the Tennessee Valley Authority and the Tennessee Valley Trades and Labor Council: A manual for Committee Members, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
    May 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Union-Management Cooperative Program in TVA, Publication (Box 110, Folder 11)
- Box: 110, Folder: 12 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Plan of Employee Representation in the Plants of Tennessee Coal, Iron and Railroad Company, Publication (Box 110, Folder 12)
- Box: 110, Folder: 13 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: TVA: A River Controlled, Publication (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: The Story of TVA, Publication (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: National Defense: Resource Development, Publication (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Industrial Development: in the TVA Area During 1965, Publication (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Industrial Development in the TVA Area During 1962, Publication (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Follies, Fallacies, and Falsehoods of Tennessee Valley Authority, Publication (Box 110, Folder 13)
    By Verne P. Kaub. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The TVA Program: A Bibliography of Selected Readings, Publication (Box 110, Folder 13)
    Revised September 1, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Indexed Bibliography of the Tennessee Valley Authority: Cumulative Supplement January 1957-December 1958, Publication (Box 110, Folder 13)
    October 1, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Supplement--Teamwork, August 1962: Committee Exhibits, Publication (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: A Short History of the Tennessee Valley Authority, Publication (Box 110, Folder 13)
    1933-1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Congressional Hearings, Reports, and Documents Relating to TVA, Publication (Box 110, Folder 13)
    1933-1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Employee Relationship Policy, Publication (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Item 13: TVA and You: A Message from the People of Tennessee, Publication (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Item 14: Organization and Development of the TVA Engineers Association, Publication (Box 110, Folder 13)
- Box: 110, Folder: 14 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Wage Negotiations in the Tennessee Valley Authority, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Pay--Salary Policy Employees, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
    August 17, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Classification of Salary Policy Positions, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
    March 7, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Uses and Preparation of Job Descriptions, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Classification of Salary Policy Positions, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
    August 19, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: WIRE Vol. 16, No. 5, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: WIRE Vol. 16, No. 3, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
    March 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: A Chronological List of Events in the Development of the TVA Salary Policy, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Plan for Management Assistant Program, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Training in TVA: Training Policy, Organization, and Objectives, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: Do You Know Your TVA?, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 12: TVA Apprenticeship Program, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
    By James P Mitchell. November 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: TVA Trades and Labor Training Past and Present, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
    June 13-14, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Cooperative Conference Bulletin Vol. 5, No. 1, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
    February 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Engineering Aide Training:Synopsis of Program, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 16: Training in TVA, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
    1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: New TVA Health Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 18: TVA Health Insurance Plan for Annual Salary Policy Employees, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 19: Medical Insurance Program for the Annual Trades and Labor Employees of Tennessee Valley Authority, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 20: Health Services For You, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 21: TVA Medical Insurance Plan for Annual Salary Policy Employees, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 22: Your TVA Retirement System, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 23: The Variable Annuity: An Optional Feature of the TVA Retirement System, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 24: TVA Health Insurance Plan for Hourly and Part-Time Employees, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 25: Voluntary Group Accident Insurance for TVA Annual Employees, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 26: News: TVA Retirement System, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 27: Report to Members 1964, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 28: Information for New Employees, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 29: What's New in Retirement, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 30: The Variable Annuity: An Optional Feature of the TVA Retirement System, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 31: Administration and Standards of Apprenticeship of the Tennessee Valley Authority, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
    June 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Administration and Standards of Apprenticeship of the Tennessee Valley Authority, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 33: Summary of Fringe Benefits for Trades and Labor Maintenance & Operating Annual Employees, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
    As of January 1, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: General Information on TVA Salaries and Related Benefits, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 35: Group Medical Insurance for Salary Policy Employees, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 36: New TVA Health Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 37: TVA Medical Insurance for Annual Salary Policy Employees, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 38: TVA Medical Insurance for Annual Salary Policy Employees, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Item 39: TVA Medical Insurance for Annual Salary Policy Employees, Publication (Box 110, Folder 14)
- Box: 110, Folder: 15 (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Working With TVA, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Management Guide for Handling Grievances of Employees Represented by the Salary Policy Employee Panal, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Working With TVA, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Tennessee Valley Authority Employee Conduct Standards and Responsibilities, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Employee Grievance Procedures, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
    By John E. Massey. July 15, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Summary Statement of TVA's Personnel Recruitment, Register, Examination, and Certification System, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Summary Statement of TVA's Personnel Recruitment, Register, Examination, and Certification System, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: TVA: Kingston Steam Plant, the World's Largest, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: Application for Employment: Tenessee Valley Authority, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: Information for Applicants about Employment in TVA, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: Employment Policy and Procedure of the Tennessee Valley Authority, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Item 12: Information for Applicants about Employment in TVA, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Item 13: Employee Contract: Tennessee Valley Authority, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Item 14: Tennessee Valley Authority: Valley of Opportunity, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Item 15: Organization Bulletin, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Item 16: Research Oppoortunities in TVA for Graduate Students and College and University Faculty Members, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Item 17: Employment Contract: Tennessee Valley Authority, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Item 18: Information for Applicants about Employment in TVA, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Item 19: Personnel Administration in TVA: A Selected List of References, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
    Revised December 1, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Tennessee Valley Authority Division of Construction: TVA Foreman's Manual, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
    July 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: A Career for Engineering Graduates with Tennessee Valley Authority, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Item 22: Information for Applicants about Employment in TVA, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Item 23: Teamwork Vol. 8, No. 1, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
    January-February 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Teamwork Vol. 8, No. 3, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
    April 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Information for Applicants about Employment in TVA, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Item 26: Tomorrow is Today in TVA, Publication (Box 110, Folder 15)